幾個世紀以來 圣殿騎士團都在尋找著神秘的伊甸蘋果
For centuries, the order of the Knights Templar have searched for the mythical Apple of Eden.
他們相信它不光包含著
They believe it contains not only
人類第一次反抗的種子
the seeds of man's first disobedience,
還有自由意志的關鍵
but the key to the free will itself.
如果他們找到遺物并解開其中的秘密
If they find the relic and decode its secrets,
他們將獲得掌控一切自由思想的力量
they will have the power to control all freedom of thought.
只有刺客兄弟會在阻止他們
Only the brotherhood called the Assassins stands in their way...
安達盧西亞 西班牙 1492年
ANDALUCIA, SPAIN 1492
宗教法庭最終還是把西班牙交給了圣殿騎士
The Inquisition has finally delivered Spain to the Templars.
蘇丹穆罕穆德和他的人仍然堅守在格拉納達
Sultan Muhammad and his people still hold out in Granada.
但如果他的兒子 王子 被抓住了
But if his son, the prince, is captured,
他將投降并交出伊甸蘋果
he will surrender the city and the Apple of Eden.
你阿吉拉爾·德·內爾哈是否
Do you, Aguilar de Nerha,
發誓在捍衛自由的戰斗中 讓我們的信條榮耀?
swear to honor our order in the fight for freedom?
守護人類抵抗圣殿騎士的暴政
To defend mankind against Templars' tyranny,
并且保護自由意志?
and preserve free will?
我發誓
I swear.
如果伊甸蘋果落入他們之手
If the Apple falls into their hands,
圣殿騎士將摧毀 擋在他們面前的一切
the Templars will destroy everything that stands in their way.
抗議異議和我們 為自己著想的權利
Protest, dissent, our right to think for ourselves.
向我發誓 你將犧牲自己的性命
Swear to me that you will sacrifice your life
和在場所有人的性命 來防止神器落入他們手中
and lives of everyone here to keep it from them.
是的導師
Yes, Mentor.
我們的生命無關緊要
Our lives are nothing.
伊甸蘋果才是一切
The Apple is everything.
雄鷹的英靈 將看守未來
The spirit of the Eagle, will watch over the future.
其他人盲目 追尋真理的時候
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
記住萬事皆虛
remember, nothing is true.
當其他人被 道德法律束縛時
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
記住事事皆允
remember, everything is permitted.
我們在黑暗中為光明服務
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們是刺客
We are Assassins.
下加利福尼亞 墨西哥 1986年
Baja California, Mexico 1986
該死
Shit.
媽媽?
Mom?
爸爸?
Dad?
你的血不只屬于你自己卡爾
Your blood is not your own, Cal.
他們找到我們了
They've found us.
活在陰影里
Live in the shadows.
逃!快逃!
Go! Go now!
30年后
30 YEARS LATER
亨茨維爾監獄 德克薩斯州美國
HUNTSVILLE PENITENTIARY, TEXAS, USA
你是來這拯救我的靈魂的吧
You're here to save my soul.
差不多把
Something like that.
我
I...
我知道今天是你生日
I understand it is your birthday.
對的
Yeah.
派對剛剛開始
The party is just getting started.
坐下你讓我緊張
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
主啊
Lord,
清洗我的罪惡
wash away my sin,
我將再次
and I'll be clean...
變干凈
Once again.
你不是個信徒對吧?
You're not much for the Bible, are you?
特告知 卡勒姆·林奇
Be it known that Callum Lynch
被認定犯一級謀殺罪
has been found guilty of capital murder
被判于今日執行死刑 2016年10月21日
and sentenced to die on this day, October 21st 2016.
犯人想做最后陳述么?
Does the prisoner wish to make a final statement?
告訴我父親咱們地獄見
Tell my father that I'll see him in hell.
我的名字是索菲亞·萊金博士
My name is Dr. Sophia Rikkin.
昨天傍晚6點 你 被處決并宣告死亡
At six pm yesterday evening, you were executed and pronounced dead.
到現在為止 如人們所知
And so far, as anyone in the world knows or cares,
你不再存在
you no longer exist.
你最好坐著
It's better you to sit.
我的眼睛
My eyes...
你現在感覺不舒服但很正常
What are you feeling right now is normal and uncomfortable.
卡爾
Cal.
我是來幫你的
I'm here to help you.
你也要幫我
And you're here to help me.
別管它
Let him go.
別碰他
Don't touch him.
繼續啊跳下去
Go ahead. Do it.
跳啊
Jump.
在這你不是囚犯卡爾
You're not a prisoner here, Cal.
我是來保護你的
I'm here to protect you.
如果你聽我的一切都說得通
If you listen to me, everything is going to make sense.
你要相信我
And you need to trust me.
我在哪兒?
Where am I?
你在阿布斯泰戈基金會 馬德里的康復區里
You're in a rehabilitation wing of Abstergo Foundation in Madrid,
一個致力于完善人類的私人組織
a private organization dedicated to the perfection of human kind.
有了你的幫助 我們能開發出消除暴力的新方法
With your help, we can pioneer new ways to eradicate violence.
我能搞定
I had this.
你父親想要抓住它
Your father wants him in.
他是我的病人
He's my patient.
這是我的項目
This is my program.
準備好Animus
Prepare the Animus.
袖劍準備好了嗎?
Are the blades prepared?
在這
Right here.
找到來源了么?
And we confirmed their provenance?
屬于阿吉拉爾
They belong to Aguilar.
我們在他的埋葬處找到它們的
We recovered them from his burial site.
這些是什么玩意兒?
What are these?
執行最后準備 我們的回歸點是安達盧西亞1492年
Assume final preparations. Our regression, Andalucía, 1492.
把所有都記錄下來
Record everything.
機械手臂準備完畢
Arms ready.
這是要干嘛?
What is this?
真不好意思卡爾這不是我做事的風格
I'm sorry, Cal, this is not the way I like to do things.
那就別這樣
Then don't do it.
注入硬脊膜外麻醉劑
Insert epidural.
你到底想從我這得到什么?
What do you want from me?
你的過去
Your past.
仔細聽我講卡爾
Listen to me carefully, Cal.
你馬上就要進入Animus
You're about to enter the Animus.
你將見到的聽到的和感受到的
What you are about to see, hear and feel,
都是某個死去500年的人的記憶
are the memories of someone who has been dead for 500 years.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你改變不了發生的事卡爾
You can't change what happens, Cal.
啟動掃描儀
Engage scanner.
狀態?
Status?
正在掃面DNA鏈 正在尋找時間框架
Scanning DNA chains. Searching for time frame.
已鎖定首段匹配記憶
First memory match locked.
已識別DNA匹配
DNA match identified.
堅持住卡爾
Stay with it, Cal.
嘗試同步
Attempt synchronization.
我們找到他了 我們找到阿吉拉爾了
We found him. We found Aguilar.
已獲得同步
Synchronization achieved.
就這樣
There.
執行回歸
Commence regression.
我們的目標是那個男孩
Our mission is the boy.
他就是王子
It's the prince.
是誰家庇護那個男孩的?
Which household harbored the boy?
就我一個
Only me.
沒人知道沒人
Nobody else knew. Nobody.
把他全家吊死給他看
Hang his family and make him watch.
燒了整個村子
Burn the whole village.
格拉納達的王子被抓住了 他父親蘇丹
With the prince of Granada as captive, his father, sultan,
將交出他的反叛城市
will surrender his rebellious city,
異教徒最后的庇護所
the last safe haven for the infidels.
上帝會懲罰他手下的異端
God will punish his people's heresy.
最終西班牙將被圣殿騎士統治
Finally Spain will be under one Templar rule.
緊盯著記憶卡爾
Stay with the memory, Cal.
阿吉拉爾!那個男孩阿吉拉爾! 那個男孩!
Aguilar! The boy, Aguilar! The boy!
那個男孩阿吉拉爾!
Aguilar, the boy!
把他拉出來!
Pull him!
執行恢復
Commence rehabilitation.
檢查一下系統 記錄他的狀態
Run a system's check, and log his condition.
干的不錯卡爾
You did well, Cal.
回首過去 很明顯
Looking back it's clear that a history
世界歷史就是暴力的歷史
of the world is history a violence.
去年反社會行為帶來的經濟損失
Last year the economic impact of antisocial behavior
高達9萬億美元
was 9 trillion dollars.
我們相信現在一個人找不到合適的出路時
We believe that man today experiences
就會采取一定的暴力
a measure of aggression which he finds no acceptable outlets.
現在想象一下如果將 這些花費引導到其他地方
Now imagine if all these costs could be channeled elsewhere...
回歸進行得好嗎?
So the regression went well?
就是林奇
Lynch is the one.
阿吉拉爾的直系后裔
Direct descendent of Aguilar.
一切都非常清晰 這還是頭一次
Everything was clear in there, for the first time.
我們都夢寐以求的是什么? 一個更和平的世界
What do we all dream of? A more peaceful world.
你又搶了我的臺詞
I see you stole my lines again.
我只搶最好的
I only steal from the best.
神器呢?
And the artifact?
伊甸蘋果 它就在我們掌控之中
The Apple. It's within our grasp.
發生了什么? 為什么把他拉出來?
What happened in there? Why did you pull him?
我必須這樣 我們必須保持他的健康
I had to. We have to keep him healthy.
獲得他的信任 我知道他會把我們引向神器的
Earn his confidence. And I know he'll lead us to it.
逼他一把
Push him.
Animus這不是這樣工作的
That's not how the Animus works.
搞定了
Here you go.
謝謝
Thank you.
1917年盧瑟福分裂了原子
1917 Rutherford splits the atom.
1953年沃森和克里克 發現了DNA雙螺旋
1953 Watson and Crick find a double helix.
2016年我的女兒
2016 my daughter
找到了治療暴力的方法
finds the cure for violence.
你總比我更聰明
You've always been brighter than me.
我遲到了
I'm late.
我要向長老匯報
I have to report to the Elders.
弗朗西斯科·利茲的 《偉大宗教法庭》1492年
Francisco Rizi's Grand Inquisition. 1492.
戰爭 宗教的控告
War, religious prosecution,
托爾克馬達神父或 任何我們組織的人
and the closest that Father Torquemada or any of our Order
最接近找到伊甸蘋果的一次
came to a finding the Apple of Eden.
你最近怎么樣我的朋友?
How are you, my friend?
還好
Well.
閣下
Your Excellency.
下周長老見面時
Next week when the Elders meet,
我們將投票結束你的 阿布斯泰戈計劃
we shall vote to discontinue your Abstergo project.
我們覺得每年給你的300萬
We feel that giving you 3 billion annually,
能花在更好的地方
could be better spent elsewhere.
3百萬算不了什么
Tri billion is nothing compared to...
我們贏了
We've won.
人們不再關注他們的公民自由
People are no longer care about their civil liberties,
他們在乎自己的生活標準
they care about their standard of life.
現代世界已經不再需要自由之類的觀念
The modern world has outgrown notions like freedom.
他們滿足于遵守
They are content to follow.
只要自由意志存在 威脅就存在
The threat remains while free will exists.
幾個世紀以來我們嘗試用 宗教、政治和現在的消費主義
For centuries we try with religion, with politics and now consumerism
來消除異議
to eliminate dissent.
難道不是時候來試一下科學嗎?
Isn't it the time we gave a science a try?
我的女兒比我們以往更接近目標
My daughter is closer than we've ever been.
你漂亮的女兒怎么樣了?
How is your beautiful daughter?
她追蹤到了伊甸蘋果的保護者
She has traced protectors of the Apple.
在哪兒?
Where?
安達盧西亞1492年
Andalucía, 1492.
后裔呢?
The descendents?
所有血脈都消亡了
All the blood lines have died out.
除了一個
But one.
我們已經追蹤了他過去的的五百年 追蹤到了刺客兄弟會
We've traced his back 500 years, to the Assassin's Brotherhood.
你的幻覺我們稱之為“出血效應”
Hallucinations are what we call the "bleeding effect."
你過去的影像
Images of your regression,
出現在你現在的視野里
laying themselves over your present day field of vision.
如果你允許 我能教你怎么控制它們
If you allow me, I can teach you how to control them.
退下都早我掌握中
Stand down. I have this.
別管他們
Let it be.
這到底是什么? 那個機器是干什么的?
What is it? The machine?
這是基因記憶
It's genetic memory.
通過Animus
By using the Animus,
我們能再歷那些造就我們的人的生活
we can relive lives of those who made us who we are.
我在那里見到的 感覺像真的
What I saw in there, it felt real.
就是真的
It was.
從某方面來說
In a way.
別惹我!
Don't mess with me!
我感覺不一樣了
I feel different now.
干嘛這么激動?
Why the aggression?
我就是個沖動的人
I'm an aggressive person.
這到底是什么監獄?
What kind of prison is this?
這不是監獄卡爾
It's not a prison, Cal.
如果你合作的話你能學到更多
You'll learn more if you cooperate.
放開我
Let me go.
我餓了
I'm hungry.
跟我來
Come with me.
林奇 1979年-現在
LYNCH 1979-present
這是什么?
What is this?
我知道你的一切卡爾
I know everything about you, Cal.
你的醫療記錄 你的心理檔案
Your medical data, your psychological profile,
你MAO-A基因里的變異
the mutations in your MAO-A gene.
我知道你的寄養家庭
I know about the foster homes.
你的青少年收容所
The juvenile homes.
你是遺傳和暴力之間關聯的活例子
You are a living proof of the link between heredity and crime.
你怎么找到我的?
How did you find me?
我們找到了阿吉拉爾
We found Aguilar.
你被捕時你的DNA和他匹配
When you were arrested, your DNA matched his.
- 阿吉拉爾是誰? - 你的祖先
- Who is Aguilar? - Your ancestor.
他的家族都是刺客
His family were Assassins.
他們被圣殿騎士、托爾克馬達
They were burnt at the stake by the Templars,
和你看到的那個黑騎士 奧赫達燒死在刑柱上
Torquemada and the black night you saw, Ojeda.
阿吉拉爾扛起了刺客的大旗
Aguilar took up the Assassins' cause.
你經常外出嗎?
Do you go out much?
比你勤
More than you.
這里的其他人呢? 他們都是小白鼠嗎?
And the others in here? Are they the lab rats too?
他們都是刺客、殺人犯  像他們的祖先一樣
They are Assassins, murderers like their ancestors.
像你一樣卡爾
Like you, Cal.
都生來帶有暴力傾向
All born with predisposition to violence.
殺人犯?
Murderer?
- 你殺了人了 - 一個皮條客
- You killed the man. - A pimp.
你還會殺人么?
Would you kill again?
快樂的一家
Happy families.
她一定非常自豪
She must be very proud.
我怎么知道
I wouldn't know.
她死于刺客之手
She was killed by an Assassin.
像你母親一樣
Like your mother.
抱歉
Sorry.
我老爹殺了我母親
My old man killed my mother.
你對此有何感受?
And how does that make you feel?
感覺和殺死他一樣
Like killing him.
要么我們任其影響我們的余生
Either we let it to effect us for the rest of our lives,
要么我們做點什么
or we just do something about it.
你投向了暴力 我投向了科學
You turn to violence, I turn to science.
這是伊甸蘋果卡爾
It's the Apple of Eden, Cal.
我相信它存在
I believe it exists.
圣經告訴我們它包含著 人類第一次反抗的種子
The Bible tells us it contained the seed of man's first disobedience.
但我們中部分人相信
But there are those of us who believe that
神或某種古代文明
God or some ancient civilization
留給了我們一個路線圖來 了解為什么人類如此暴力
have left us a road map to understand why people are violent.
阿吉拉爾是我們所知的 最后一個擁有伊甸蘋果的人
Aguilar was the last person known to have had it in his possession.
我們需要你找出他把它藏在哪里了
We need you to find out where he hid it.
我以為我是來接受治療的
I thought I was here to be cured.
暴力就是種疾病
Violence is a disease.
像癌癥一樣
Like cancer.
并且像癌癥一樣 我們希望有一天能治愈它
And like cancer, we hope to control it one day.
是暴力讓我還活著
Violence is what kept me alive.
好吧 嚴格地說你死了
Well technically, you're dead.
我餓了
I'm hungry.
我有什么好處?
What's in it for me?
一旦我的研究完成 這里就不需要你了
Once my research is complete, there is no reason to keep you here.
我能回到自己的生活?
I get my life back?
比那更好你將有個新生活
Better. A new one.
你不是餓了么
You are hungry.
你不知道他是誰 他是干什么的
You don't know who he is, what he is.
他是個危險人物
He is a dangerous man.
多給他點時間埃米爾
Give him little more time, Emir.
他或許能證明他的骨子里流著高貴的血
Man may prove that has some noble blood in him yet.
坐這里怎么樣先生?
How about, sir?
可以隨便點菜 但我們推薦雞
It's an open menu, but we do recommend a chicken.
你想要點什么 林奇先生? 可以隨便點菜
What can I get you, Mr. Lynch? It's an open menu,
但我們推薦雞
but we do recommend a chicken.
我要牛排
I'll steak.
給開拓者一份牛排
Steak for the pioneer.
你是誰?
Who are you?
他們叫我穆薩
They call me Moussa.
但我的名字是巴普蒂斯特 我已經死了200年了
But my name is Baptiste. I'm dead 200 years now.
伏都毒師
Voodoo poisoner.
我不會傷害任何人
I'm harmless.
他們在盯著你
They're watching you.
等著發現你是誰開拓者
Waiting to see who you are, pioneer.
你見過他了么?
Have you met him yet?
你有沒有見過他?
我們都是最后保護伊甸蘋果的人我的朋友
We are the last to protect the Apple, my friend.
做錯一個選擇 你將把我們都送入無底深淵
Pick the wrong choice, you'll send us all to infinity.
這個
This...
是你的
belongs to you.
你將把他們直接引向它
You're going to lead them right to it.
不我打算吃了它
Ne, I'm going to eat it.
什么鬼?
What the fuck is going on?
他必須回到Animus
He has to go back in the Animus.
現在
Now.
在再次進入之前他還需要點時間
He needs more time before he goes in again.
我們沒時間了
We don't have time.
為什么?
Why?
我不會拿他的命冒險
I won't risk his life.
那么我就找其他人來做
Then I'll have to find someone else to do it.
- 該你上了高手 - 我已經瘋了
- You're up, slugger. - I'm crazy.
我已經瘋了
I'm crazy.
因感到寂寞而瘋
Crazy for feeling so lonely.
他們又讓他進去了
They're getting him back in again.
我們必須在他背叛我們之前阻止他
We should stop him before he betrays us.
日期調到6
Set the date for the six.
如果他狀態惡化 就拉他出來
If his condition deteriorates, pull him out.
- 你父親 - 我不管我爸說了什么
- You father... - I don't care what my father said.
我在世上到底做了什么?
What in the world did I do?
- 卡爾聽我說 - 我為嘗試瘋狂
- Cal, listen to me. - I'm crazy for trying...
聽我說 你必須緊盯著阿吉拉爾
Listen to me. You have to stay with Aguilar.
為哭泣瘋狂
Crazy for crying...
呆在同步空白處很危險
Staying in synch-void could be dangerous.
我為愛你而瘋狂
And I'm crazy for loving you...
很快他們將進軍格拉納德
Soon they will march on Granada.
蘇丹穆罕穆德已經虛弱了
Sultan Muhammad is weak.
他將交出伊甸蘋果
He'll surrender the Apple
并且為了救王子背叛信條
and betray the Creed to save the prince.
愛讓我們變弱
The love makes us weak.
值得高興的是我將犧牲我的血肉
Gladly I'll sacrifice my flesh and blood,
讓信條得以幸存
for survival of the Creed.
當我今天死去時 別為我浪費眼淚
When I die today, don't waste your tears for me.
主發話了
The Lord spoke.
他說:
And he said:
"如果一個人不遵從我
"If a man abide not in me
他就會被投入火中
he is cast into the fire
并且被燒死!"
and he is burned!"
數十年來
For decades,
你們因宗教不同
you have lived in the world torn apart
生活在四分五裂的世界
by religious discord.
但很快感謝上帝
But soon, thanks to God
和宗教法庭
and Inquisition
我們將清洗這一疾病!
we will purge this disease!
你們面前的這些罪人
The sinners before you,
在這場圣戰中致力于保護
sought to defend the heretic prince of Granada,
野蠻人最后的據點格拉納德
the last heathen stronghold
的異教徒的王子
in our holy war.
所以今天
So today,
在我們的國王及皇后面前
before our king and queen
我發誓我將在上帝的圣火中
I swear we shall wash ourselves clean,
凈化我們自己!
in the holy fire of God!
看啊
Behold...
上帝的意志!
God's will!
你將看著你們的導師被燒死 然后以最慢的方式死去
You will watch your mentor burn and then you will die the slowest.
給未來帶來榮耀
Give glory to the future.
而不是給我們
Not to us.
他正在同步
He is synchronizing.
該死的異教徒!
Damned heretics!
別讓他們跑了!
Don't let them escape!
跳
Jump.
同步消除完畢
Complete desynch.
放他下來!
Get him down!
叫醫生!
Call the medics!
沒事了沒事了 卡爾醒醒卡爾
Okay. It's okay. Cal, stay with me. Cal.
穩住 沒事了 快點!
Stay... It's okay. Hurry up!
好了好了 看著我
Okay. Okay. Look at me.
看著我
Look at me.
我的腿沒知覺了
I can't feel my legs.
癱瘓是暫時的
Paralysis is temporal.
壞消息呢?
What's the bad news?
它造成了神經分裂  但是我們帶你挺過來了
It caused a neurological split but we got you through it.
這一次
This time.
我會死在這兒對吧?
I'm gonna die in here, aren't I?
不會
No.
只要你自愿進入那里就不會死
Not if you go in there on your own free will.
我辦不到
I can't do this.
不你行的
Yes, you can.
那個伊甸蘋果你是僅存的能找到它的人
The Apple. You're the only one left who can find it.
我們能結束這些痛苦卡爾
We can put an end to pain, Cal.
為所有人
For everyone.
你從哪兒得到它的?
Where did you get this?
我父親從你母親的謀殺現場取來的
My father recovered it from the scene of your mother's murder.
并帶到這里保管
And brought it here for safekeeping.
保管?
Safekeeping?
你偷了它
You stole it.
這是你母親的項鏈 我希望你拿著它
It's your mother's necklace. I wanted you to have it.
他為什么在這?
Why was he there?
- 為了救她 - 從誰手里?
- To save her. - From whom?
- 她自己的人 - 和你有什么關系?
- Her own people. - What's that got to do with you?
刺客和圣殿騎士的戰爭 持續了幾個世紀了
Assassins and Templars have been at war for centuries.
我想改變它
I aim to change that.
哦對我忘了
That's right, I forgot.
我們是來和侵略作斗爭的
We're here to combat aggression.
我不喜歡你的方法
I don't think I like your methods.
我是科學家
I am a scientist.
我是來治療暴力的
I'm here to be cured of violence.
誰來治愈你?
Who's gonna cure you?
我們在喂養野獸
We're feeding the beast.
我們在使他變得更強
We're making him stronger.
我是萊金博士
I am Dr Rikkin.
艾倫
Alan.
我在阿布斯泰戈這里負責照看一些事物
I look after things here in Abstergo.
你喜歡把事物 放在一個大家庭里是吧?
You like to keep the things in the family, huh?
是的
Yes.
很抱歉讓你感到不舒服
I'm sorry if we caused you any discomfort.
我還能為你做什么?
Is there anything I can do?
放了我怎么樣?
How about you let me out of here?
這我辦不到
That's something I can't manage.
我是來做交易的
I'm here to make a deal.
我們需要伊甸蘋果
We need the Apple.
需要你為我們找到它
And we need you to get it for us.
你已經和Animus消除同步了
You've been desynching in the Animus.
我們希望你不要這樣
We need you not to do that.
把我送回機器里?
Sending me back to the machine?
不 你已經給我們看了我們需要看到的
No, you've already shown us what we needed to see.
那你會放我們走嗎?
Will you let us free then?
你想從新來的那里獲得什么?
What do you hope to gain from the newcomer?
一些有益我們所有人的東西
Something that'll benefit us all.
還有你穆薩
You too, Moussa.
你對他們做了什么?
What have you done to them?
當你不是自愿回到過去時就會這樣
It's what happens if you don't enter in regression on your own volition.
你認出這個了嗎?
Do you recognize this?
這是刺客的袖劍
It's Assassin's blade.
這就是那把
This is the actual one...
你父親用來殺死你母親的刀
your father used to take your mother's life.
他也在這你知道嗎?
He's here, you know?
母親的死卡爾
Mother's death, Cal.
可不是什么應該讓孩子看到的東西
Not something a boy should ever be made to see.
這是錯的
This is wrong.
你逼我的
You left me no choice.
他必須以自己的意志進入你說的
He has to go in on his own free will, you said that.
- 我必須協商 - 你是說操控?
- I had to negotiate. - You mean manipulate?
我向長老保證我們會為倫敦獲得伊甸蘋果
I assured the Elders we would have the Apple for London.
在兩天內
That's in two days.
他不想知道他的過去 或他父親的
He doesn't want to know his past, or his father.
他想摧毀他們全部
He wants to destroy them, both.
我們不是來制造怪物的
We're not in the business of creating monsters.
我們既不會制造他們也不會毀滅他們
We neither created them nor destroyed them.
我們只不過任他們沉溺于 自己不可動搖的信仰
We merely abandoned them to their own inexorable faith.
- 你是你母親的兒子 - 什么意思?
- You're your mother's son. - What does that mean?
你體內流動的血不只是你自己的
Blood that flows through you is not your own.
還屬于信條
Belongs to the Creed.
你母親知道的
Your mother knew that.
她死了信條才得以存活
She died so the Creed may live.
告訴我為什么會這樣!
Remind me how, exactly!
你看到的確實是我做的
What you saw, I did.
你謀殺了她
You murdered her.
我寧可奪去她的生命也不想它讓機器偷取
I took her life rather than have it stolen by that machine.
使命讓人偉大
Man grows with the greatness of his task.
我本應殺了你
I ought to have killed you.
我下不了手
I couldn't.
那么現在
Well, here.
殺了我
Take it.
做你30年前做不了的事
Do what you couldn't do 30 years ago.
刀在你手里卡爾
It's in your hands now, Cal.
這就是他們想要的
This is what they want.
讓我留血
Spill my blood.
但是別再回機器里了
But do not go back in the Animus.
為什么?
Why?
伊甸蘋果包含了自由意志的基因編碼
The Apple contains the genetic code for free will.
他們會用它毀了我們
They will use it to destroy us.
我要找到它
I'm gonna find it.
然后看著他們摧毀你和你的信條
And watch them destroy you and your Creed.
你毀不掉信條
You can not kill the Creed.
它在你的血液里
It's in your blood.
伊甸蘋果就是一切
The Apple is everything.
你母親為保護它而死
Your mother died to protect it.
她沒得選
She had no choice.
我有
I do.
你會毀了信條!
You're gonna kill the Creed!
帶我去Animus
Take me to the Animus.
把我放進去
Put me in.
準備好Animus
Prepare the Animus.
自愿回歸
Voluntary regression.
你知道刺客名字的由來嗎?
Do you know how the Assassins came to be named?
來自阿拉伯語 "Hashashin"
From an Arabic word "Hashashin".
他們是被社會排斥的人
They were society's outcasts.
那些冷血偷竊、謀殺的人
Those who stole, who murdered in cold blood.
人們嘲笑他們 叛逆者愚蠢的人癮君子
People ridiculed them... Rebels, fools, drug addicts.
但他們是智慧的
But they were wise.
他們利用這個名聲來向那些甚至最強的敵人
They used this reputation to hide the dedication to principles
隱藏自己所獻身原則的
beyond those of even their strongest enemies.
我為此敬佩他們
And for that I admire them.
但你不是其中之一
But you're not one of those men.
那你是嗎?
Are you?
走著瞧吧
Let's find out.
啟動回歸
Commencing regression.
這是我一生的工作
This is my life's work.
這是我的生活
It's my life.
為了信條
For the Creed.
我們的生命
Our own lives...
我們所留下的才是重要的
What matters is what we leave behind.
蘇丹
Sultan...
交出伊甸蘋果
Surrender the Apple.
你的刺客保護者都沒了
Your Assassin protectors are gone.
信條完了
The Creed is finished.
我的孩子
My son.
這里埋藏著
Here lies the seed
人類第一次反抗的種子
of man's first disobedience,
自由意志的種子
of free will itself.
多虧了伊甸蘋果
Thanks to the Apple of Eden,
我們所知的世界
the known world
將被領入新時代
shall be ushered into a new age.
一個和平時代
One of peace,
所有戰爭中的人
in which all the warring populations of mankind
將完全只服從于
shall bow in perfect obedience
我們圣殿騎士的統治
to our one templar rule.
伊甸蘋果
The Apple.
給他
Give it to him.
現在
Now.
為了信條
For the Creed.
上!
Go!
原諒我
Forgive me.
結束了!
It's over!
刺客!
Assassin!
信仰之躍
A leap of faith.
我們在哪兒?
Where are we?
看起來像軍港
It looks like a military port.
卡的斯帕洛斯-德拉弗龍特拉
Kadiz, Palos de la Frontera.
刺客為它而死
The Assassins died for it.
用你的生命保護它
Protect it with your life.
我是信條的朋友
I am a friend of the Creed.
把它帶入你的墳墓
Take it to your grave.
我發誓
I swear.
這是什么? 翻譯
What is it? Translation.
循著陽光 我將拋下這舊世界
Following the light of the sun, I shall leave this old world behind.
是克里斯托弗·哥倫布
It's Christopher Columbus.
他被埋在哪兒?
Where is he buried?
他的遺體回到了西班牙
His remains were returned to Spain.
他的陵墓在塞維利亞大教堂
His tomb is in Seville Cathedral.
我們找到它了
We found it.
嘿全明星過來
Hey All Stars, come here.
挑一個
Pick one.
隨便哪個
Anyone.
- 公共休息室被突破 - 封鎖Animus
- Breach in common room. - Seal the Animus.
這是記憶么?
Is it a memory?
不是
No.
來吧!
Come on!
- 轉運? - 準備就緒了
- Transport? - Standing by.
保護Animus 清理整個設施
Protect the Animus. Purge the facility.
我要先帶你離開這兒
I need to get you out of here first.
- 不! - 我們必須離開索菲亞
- No! - We have to leave, Sophia.
不!
No!
把它撿起來!
Pick it up!
你不是孤軍奮戰卡爾
You are not alone, Cal.
你從來不是
You never were.
- 打開 - 來吧
- Open... - Come on.
其他人盲目 追尋真理的時候
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
- 記住 - 萬事皆虛
- remember... - Nothing is true.
當其他人被 道德法律束縛時
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
- 記住 - 事事皆允
- remember... - Everything is permitted.
我們在黑暗中為光明服務
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們是刺客
We are Assassins.
現在怎么辦 開拓者?
What now, pioneer?
我們打
We fight.
閣下
Your Excellency.
榮耀屬于你父親
The glory will go to your father.
但我們都知道是誰發現了它
But we both know who found it.
屬于你的時刻回來的孩子
Your time will come, my child.
圣殿騎士圣堂 倫敦
GREAT TEMPLAR LODGE, LONDON P s a g m e n o .com
他們會因此給你個諾貝爾和平獎
They'll give you a Nobel peace prize for this.
你最好開始寫演講稿
You better start writing your speech.
- 我讀了你的 - 然后呢?
- I've read yours. - And?
如果我們消滅了自由意志 我們就消滅了刺客
If we eradicate free will, we eradicate the Assassins.
一個威脅了世界幾個世紀的癌癥
A cancer that has menaced society for centuries.
這不是我最好的作品 但它能表達我的意思
It's not my best work, but it gets the point across.
我們一直在尋找解決途徑
We've been looking for solutions.
你已經消除了問題
You've eliminated the problem.
那么我的計劃
So my program...
第一次給社會帶來秩序
Has brought order to society for the first time.
我對此負責
I'm accountable for this.
你已經盡責了
You've already been accounted for.
我們的成果屬于長老
Our work belongs to the Elders.
這是他們最美好的時光
This is their finest hour.
你對我撒謊了
You lied to me.
我一直知道
I've always known
在你心里你永遠首先是個科學家 然后才是圣殿騎士
that in your heart you're a scientist first, templar second.
你最近的成果令人刮目相看
Your recent work has impressed as much
但它讓我們堅信
but it has confirmed our belief that mankind
人類無法被拯救
cannot be redeemed.
一切都被你料到了
You've thought of everything.
也不盡然我的演講 需要你優雅的開場白
Not quite. My speech. It could do with one of your elegant openings.
“現在我成了世界的
Now I've become death,
死亡和毀滅者”
the destroyer of worlds.
這好像不行
Not sure that I could make that work.
今晚我很高興能介紹
It is with great pleasure tonight that I introduce
我們古老教團的未來的建筑師
the architect of our ancient order's future.
請歡迎阿布斯泰戈基金會的CEO
Please welcome the CEO of Abstergo Foundation,
艾倫·萊金博士
Dr. Alan Rikkin.
隨著伊甸蘋果的發現
With the recovery of the Apple,
我們獲得了
we are now in possession
人類本性的
of the complete genetic road map
完整基因路線圖
to humanity's instincts.
任何對獨立、抵抗、
Any impulse towards independence,
造反的沖動
resistance or rebellion
將被鏟除
will be crushed.
任何反抗我們前進步伐的傾向
Any predisposition that might oppose our march of progress
現在都能被消滅
can now be eradicated.
我所需做的就是大叫
All I have to do is shout.
我是來幫你的
I'm here to help you.
你也要幫我
And you're here to help me.
我幫不了你了
I can't help you anymore.
那些偉大的計劃呢?
What about all those great plans?
治愈暴力 和侵略作斗爭
Cure violence, combat aggression.
那就是馬上要發生的
That's not going to happen.
你造成了這一切索菲亞 你逃避不了
You've started this, Sophie. You don't get to walk away.
我們都知道接下來會發生什么
We both know what happens next.
不是所有事物都值得存活
Not everything deserves to live.
我辦不到
I can't do this.
不你能行
Yes, you can.
但不是給我們自己
But it is not to ourselves,
而是給未來 我們必須獻出榮耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.
一個清除刺客的未來!
A future purged of the Assassin's Creed!
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
伊甸蘋果
the Apple of Eden.
是我干的
I did this.
我會為長老們取回神器的
I will retrieve the artifact for the Elders.
我想要抓到林奇
Lynch I want for me.
不是給我們自己
It is not to ourselves,
而是給未來 我們必須獻出榮耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.